Welcome back everyone and.
Due to popular demand
and bringing Fred back
after.
Our cancer interview there's so many
questions that video hit over a million views
and there's a lot of
questions so we want to
talk about.
What
to eat.
Once you get cancer now
there is a diet to prevent
cancer which you know i i i really
i think it's going
to be healthy keto
fasting but.
Once you get cancer what do you eat
so that's we're going to talk about today.
So welcome Fred.
I have thanks for
having me again.
Absolutely for those of you that haven't
seen the first video i'm going to put that
link down below.
But in a thumbnail sketch.
And
you had a tumor.
That was
how large was it
fifteen centimeters.
Ten centimeters
ten centimeters okay.
In your Colin and
within four months.
Ah it shrank down to nothing so.
It was a stage three
borderline states for it was a.
Remarkable what you did and so
we want to talk about exactly the
details because there's so many questions.
Is that correct you've been
getting a lot of questions.
Yeah yeah absolutely
to the point that i couldn't
answer everyone
and i apologize if.
I had questions on my YouTube channel i
received email messages i tried to answer
everybody or as much as i
could underneath your video.
Please allow time so.
I'm really glad you invited me to a to a
question and answer so that's going to be
it's going to be
much easier for me.
Yes.
And just to make a disclaimer anything that
i say is not meant to diagnose or replace
your medical care check with your doctor
before implementing anything we're gonna
talk about.
And
we have no buy
them wants to sell you
and.
So.
That's my disclaimer.
And.
I want to just jump right in and a
really important part of this program is
fasting.
Twenty one day fast
so i guess the first question.
You know when you
when you tell someone they
have to fast for twenty one days.
That probably gonna.
Freak out
so.
How how is it possible that you
can fast for twenty one days i mean.
I mean aren't you going
to starve to death like what
how would you
respond to that question.
Well first
it's important to know
that i didn't jump into.
Into some guy nuff woo hoo e p.
Treatment.
I was followed by it by my oncologist
both in France and in the u s all the time
and i made my research
and you don't want to bet
my life on someone told me
well yeah you know you should
fast when you have cancer
so i read all the
scientific literature.
I rent all of doctor domestic friends or
research doctor wanted was the longest suit
your research
and at some point.
I discovered your video
which
and i'm very i'm being very honest
with it's really really really helped me.
And but yeah i made
the research and the the
twenty one day.
Water fast.
Seems to be
some kind of a of a of a.
Perfect time
to to help with cancer.
And the
like we discussed
in the previous video.
And
i'm completely aware that i was
in the perfect condition to do that
and everybody needs to make his own research
to adapt to his own lifestyle level of
stress weight
talk to your doctor
does a lot of things i mean
don't just do what i did.
What i'm trying to do
huh and i talked to you
doctor burden unto
your enter your members
and is simply to share
my experience and tell you.
There is a possibility to do something
else or to add something to your treatment
there there's some research that you can
do that that's what i'm trying to do do.
And as far as the twenty
one day fast whites
it's very easy you
know you all know now
following dr berg's the
principle of pathology.
Which is basically when
you're healthy sales has nothing
have nothing to eat.
Instead of dying of hunger.
They will feed
on your non healthy
cells
so basically the
healthy cells will
will
eat
literally eat the cancer cells
and that's that's
the reason why.
Fasting is so powerful
when you have cancer
and that's what i did.
And.
Twenty one days not fun
and like i said the other day
if i were to do it today
i would probably fail
because i don't have.
The a good reason
to do it even though
fasting is always healthy
but when when someone tells you
you're probably going to die you know
and all the research seemed to.
Indicate that if you fast
this is not going to happen.
You just do it
you know it's not the
it's not even a question.
So that's why.
It was not.
That
hard
but was i weak
was i tired yes of course.
Did i spend most of
my twenty one days
lying down on my bed
yeah
absolutely.
Did i lose weight
yeah.
That too.
Did i feel great no
absolutely not
but.
It worked.
After i had my first mri before
and on my second a mri after
the twenty one day fast
and the results were here that
schumer went from ten centimeters to five.
You know.
When you're dealing with
a life or death situation.
Mostly apple will do
whatever they can.
And it also requires fasting
and the thing about fasting
is what you guys need
to know as it's the most
important thing you can do
because of all the different.
Things that kick in
from a genetic level
to hormone level like the
growth hormones go down
and
the cancer cells.
Start committing
suicide because.
When you don't
eat your body goes in
this hyper survival mode.
And.
And it starts to survey vibe better and so
you get all the cancer genes that turn off
and then.
Your your cells actually
recycle.
The cancer cells for food.
So that's a great.
Great thing to be able to turn your cancer
cells into food for your normal cells that.
I mean there's just so much
research on this and i think.
It's important to.
Do.
Not just blindly follow
anyone to really get the data
study it
and unfortunately
there's a lot of big.
Terminal term new terms
when you read the research
so you're going to have to get.
Several dictionaries out you're going
to have to get a medical dictionary
and you're going to have to
understand some of these 'em.
The study so you can have
the confidence to know that.
You know
it can it can work for you.
And
you are you are so right when you say that
because one of the first thing that i did.
When i learned
that i had cancer.
Was to educate myself.
What is cancer what
do we know about it.
And the
one of the thing that i
always tell people is.
My shield from cancer
by trusting the science
and not the doctors.
And i'm not.
Throwing a stone at
the doctors not at all
but.
Not everybody's up to date
with the the latest research
and when you start reading.
Twenty twenty two
twenty twenty one.
Two thousand
all those latest
research on cancer and fasting and
cancer and a ketogenic diet and genser as a
metabolic disease.
You learn so much that.
You're.
Or at least my oncologist
didn't fill me up.
So.
Getting educated and taking
your health into your own hands.
Is the key to
whatever i did and that
the only thing that i
will recommend people.
Yeah i mean.
In a thumbnail sketch of the
way you solve problems is by.
Understanding.
The problem more.
That always seemed
to solve any problem i.
Okay so now
i.
Did you have you didn't really have a lot
of weight to lose when you did this right
so you did get skinny
and you went from
what weight to what way.
I went from seventy
kilos to forty nine kilos
okay.
So.
Sorry i don't know what it is in pounds
but basically i i went from a very healthy
and fit.
Body composition
to nothing but bones.
Okay.
As far as.
During the fasting period
and.
We're not oh let's not talk
about the supplements first but.
What about did you have
anything you had did you have
coffee you didn't you take water
was there anything juices
that you have anything
to eat.
So that's one of the.
Number one question and
i received
from.
From the people is what did you
eat during your twenty one day fast
and the answer is nothing.
It was nuts
it was not intermittent fasting and
people really have to make the difference.
It was not a juice
fast or a raw food fast.
It was a fast
period so i didn't eat anything
in twenty one days.
I mostly had water.
And i was supposed to drink.
One little shop
of wheatgrass
juice freshly pressed
wheatgrass juice every day
which i didn't because.
It tastes horrible.
Until
and here again
thank you dr berg.
Until i saw your video on the
your wheatgrass juice powder
which i bought immediately
unchanged my life
and
i'm not getting paid to say
that i have no personal interest
i'm just saying
because it's the truth
and from that moment it was much
easier for me to consume a little bit.
Of wheatgrass juice.
When i needed it.
So basically i dunno maybe
three four times a week.
I would have a little shot
of regress juice
and that was it so water
most of the time
and with pressed juice
once in a while.
That's all i had for
twenty one days.
Okay now let's shift to the supplements
because that's an important question.
For those of you that
are new watching this.
I study.
Myself.
Tighten the bomb
and a lot of you viewers that
are watching right now donated to.
This cancer research
we did in Europe.
With the help of.
Maurice.
Israel who is a professor
and
his his md.
And as a medical doc or as
well as his phd in biochemistry.
A very very smart.
Person who helped
us set up this study.
He found some
fascinating fascinating
and.
Data it.
As far as the weak link of
cancer the achilles heel the
the area where.
It's a really big difference between
a cancer cell and a normal self and.
And without getting into any technical
things there's a there's a door that.
Goes in the cancer that allows
the cancer cells to
make membranes.
And without those membranes
the cancer cell cannot.
Survive
and so this metabolic
enzyme.
Name.
The initials are Scott.
And so
if you could
potentially block this enzyme.
You could starve the
cancer not from fuel
but from.
Its
raw material
it's structure its membrane.
So.
The problem is.
Well.
Most came
not most but a
handful of chemo drugs.
Then it could be most i dunno.
I
actually block Scott.
But they also kill the cancer
and they kill your immune
system and it just
so happens even
a cancer cell itself.
Is and.
Has some of your own
immune cells in the cancer
tumor itself or the
cancer.
So in other words 'em.
We wanted to find a natural way to block
Scott without the t toxic effect destroying
your immune system.
Well
and.
He did some.
Previous research and
he found great success
so what we did is we
do.
Did.
That research and
we compared it to.
One of the most
powerful chemo drugs
to see how it compared.
Andor.
I did very well
i did a summary of that.
That steady I'll put
that link down below.
But anyway there are certain
nutrients that can block this enzyme
to
potentially close the door on.
The reproduction of the cancer.
Cell and then you took.
Like the two
the two big ones
are Alpha lipoic acid
and a
garcinia cambogia
so you sir tell us a
little bit about Tom
the supplements that you took.
Cause i know there isn't a lot
of extra things you took as well.
Yeah absolutely
and.
Please forgive me if i if i.
Use.
A little
of notes.
Because i don't want to
forget any thing for your.
For your followers.
All the things that i
that i put in my book.
Helps me with the timeline and remembering
what i did when he goes as you can imagine
i was.
My rain was.
Pretty much frozen when
they told me i had cancer and
and.
I had
big
chances to die.
So.
Sometimes i don't remember what i
did when it gets a little confusing so
i take my own book
and i and i take a look.
So basically yes what i did was the
twenty one day fast then strict ketogenic
diet
one hundred percent organic
and
the supplements.
So the supplements just to make sure i
don't forget anything i'm going to i'm going
to read my own book and
and take a look at it the view.
If you allow me.
Man so basically
this is what i did.
I used.
Vitamin d three.
Vitamin c.
Turmeric.
Zinc.
Omega threes.
In the form of fish oil
and in the form of d h eight.
Then i also used.
The famous and
metabolic.
Treatments that you
just mentioned from.
From professor moyes Israel.
Which is made of
Alpha-lipoic acid.
Garcinia Cambodia.
Garlic.
Or garlic extract.
What else but
bu.
Oh yes and.
Melatonin.
Is a new one
high doses of Melatonin in my case it was
anywhere between twenty and thirty grams.
And.
Drama Lane.
And i think that's about it.
So.
Much i hadn't.
Yet got much a green
tea matcha green tea yeah
okay so those are the
supplements that i used.
Great and will put those
down in the description but
but the the big thing that.
I wanted to sir
just mentioned will briefly.
Do.
Some of the like Melatonin.
Also.
Allison from the garlic.
And.
Are also
Scott inhibitors so
there's actually
many Scott and Harrison
and that is the next
thing we're looking at is to.
Take all these natural
Scott inhibitors and.
Evaluate which ones
are the strongest to the.
The weakest and
but.
You know at this point.
We haven't done that
test so we're going to
include
quite a few of the inhibitors
and Melatonin is another.
Potent.
Compound for cancer and of
course so is garlic and so as green tea
green tea.
Also blocks.
The.
Cancer from consuming.
Glutamine.
Which is very very awesome
but it does other things too so.
So in other words Maurice Israel looked
at the camera the the whole biochemistry of
what happens
in cancer.
And he really studied what things need
to be blocked in what we could use to help.
Block.
From going the front and
the back and the back door
i'm telling you these these
cancer cells are really sneaky
so you have to use strategies
to.
Handle this problem
from all angles
so.
So you took these
natural remedies.
And
you also
i think you add sea salt to
write because that's input rd
and
some of the other vitamins you
took because you're not eating food.
You're going to have to
take these vitamins because.
Your health depends on it so.
You didn't eat food but
you had nutrients which
are not going to break the fast and what
we're trying to do here because they're.
Providing something that you're
really missing when you're not eating.
Yeah
so on my side
it was
it was a.
Hard decision.
As to.
Do i take my supplements
when i'm fasting or not
and.
I was gonna
and that's why i suggest
people do and guy
as you know did it
but me my empty
stomach couldn't take.
The vitamins and mineral
supplements when i was fasting
so no i didn't take anything.
For the twenty one days
and i started supplementing after the fast
but it's not what i recommended because i
have a very sensitive stomach
and i just couldn't
i took one bite them in
with a little bit of water and
two minutes later
my stomach hurt.
But yeah usually.
Married
marries his royal anniston.
I
suggest that you keep
taking those supplements
as
your fasting definitely.
The omega three fatty acids are.
Composed of d h a
and e pa those are.
Fish oils and
those are really really
really important as well and.
Especially for.
Their anti cancer so
of course everything.
That you mentioned is.
Has
other additional anti cancer properties like
the turmeric for example and rumbling so
and.
I think.
You you
you're just basically hitting it from a
lotta different angles because you did the
research and you found wow this.
This could work.
Yes absolutely so first.
My oncologist friend in Paris.
Who is aware of.
Morrissey's around in
his work and at the time.
Lol Schwartz's work.
Told me okay Fred
you gotta start taking.
Melatonin Melatonin right away
high doses of Melatonin
you have to start taking.
A green tea thinking.
Garlic
so he was aware of
the of the protocol which
was not as complete
as the time as it is now.
And then a little bit later.
I discovered read.
Through your channel
and and a common friend
guy i.
Contacted him
and got the whole the full protocol
and that's that's how i continued.
My.
My treatment so to speak.
Okay.
So then when you
ate
okay so you went twenty
will first of all like how many.
You you had four months right so did you
start off with a twenty one day faster what
did you
what type of fasting
and i think he was even for five days
not on the rican so just kind of explain.
The details on that so so.
When i was nine diagnosed.
I was really really down completely
frozen i couldn't make any decision
just thinking i was going
to die for three days.
And after the three days
i kicked myself in the
bud then i said okay.
I'm going to survive this i'm going to
do whatever it takes but i'm going to
survivors and that's where
i started doing my research
so almost immediately i went
on a strict
twenty one day fast water fast.
After that.
I went on a strict organic
ketogenic diet then we can go
through what i ate if you want to.
And for three months
and almost at the end
i didn't know i was almost cure and the
time we just knew that the tumor was getting
smaller and smaller
but he was still here.
I went for another
twenty one day fast
but only fasting
five days a week
and eating normally
a normal ketogenic diet
during the weekends.
And so.
The goal that is so you started
with a twenty one day fast.
Then you went to
one meal a day
and then you went back to.
A twenty one days
of really like five.
Days of fasting and then
two days of one meal a day.
Exactly the tone.
Okay yes.
And okay so then
when you did eat.
Coming off of the twenty
one day fast of course
you had to gradually
introduce food right.
Yes
so let's
talk about what how did you gradually
injured his food what did you eat.
What first i was on a strict
ketogenic diet so zero zero carbs
or as close to zero as i could.
No sugar not even fruits
and.
Basically i was left with
proteins fats and veggies
so i tried
and i went on a.
On a on a quest almost discover
what can i eat and why couldn't
and most of what i ate.
Get me so much pain i was in so much
pain at the time because of the cancer.
So the only thing i could eat and i
discovered that throughout several days.
Was.
Freshly pressed
vegetable juice.
Beef.
One hundred percent
grass fed grass finished beef
and mostly revise which.
For me was the perfect balance of
not too much protein and enough fat.
And good fats avocado.
Coconut oil.
Grass fed butter.
French heavy cream.
That's all i could eat it
sold for three and a half month
all i ate was.
Vegetable juice
and ribeye steak.
The next David devil juice and ribeye steak
and the day after that vegetable juice
and ribeye steaks
that's what i ate.
And.
Again or one of your video really
helped me because when i discovered
that glutamine could
also feed cancer.
In in in certain conditions.
But that green tea.
Could help her that's
what i did was.
Break my fast every day
with a fresh vegetable juice.
Then.
About an hour later
had my steak and avocado
and about.
Five to ten minutes after that.
A big.
Glass of green tea
to help control roll
the glutamine from the stake
and that was my meal
every single day
for almost three months.
Okay.
Good so that helps out
and
and then.
As far as quantity of what you
did you just pretty
much eat enough.
So you can be filled
because your
stomach when fasting
kind of shrinks since you're not able to
probably the quantities that you normally.
Well.
I can eat
the mother or that i can eat so
before cancer.
If i had
if i had pizza for example i wouldn't have
wanted i wouldn't have two bids as i have
for pizza
i can eat.
Of course i couldn't eat the same thing and
not in the same quantity when i was sick
but.
At least
a one pound
ribeye
it was my.
Basic
quantity.
Once a day.
Yet once a day.
A big glass of fresh
seasonal vegetables.
A big
one one pound
ribeye cooked in butter
or olive oil with a pinch in
a
Milan salt
or sea salt.
And migrant he.
Does basically
what i ate every day
and what to do what type
of i supposed to do juice.
Anything
anything that was
organic
and in season.
So
during the summer
i juiced a ladder for
a spinach and cabbage
and stuff like that.
During the winter.
When we went more into the
spring i just cucumbers and celery
so it really i just
took whatever.
The farmers market
was offering me.
At that particular time.
But as many veggies as possible
drains
colored.
To have as much micronutrients
as i could that was my goal
to really.
Push.
The micro nutrition into my body
and to help my body
fight that cancer.
There are so many things so many anti
cancer every time you look up the benefit of
any vegetable even beets
and carrots and everything.
It they will always say
to them any accident has.
It
has anti-inflammatory
anti cancer.
Properties.
But i think also you had
a cruciferous vegetables too right oh
yes glorious a lot of a lot of broccoli is
and the two have
even more effect
i used a lot
i juiced a lot of
broccoli sprouts.
So.
I put the sprouts
in neiges
in the in the juicer i'm in.
And the just extract
the nutrients from
the broccoli sprouts
and yeah
that was.
Mainly.
All my juices.
All my juices in addition
to the seasonal vegetable
i always added
broccoli sprouts
and turmeric
those are the two
things that were
that were here in NY juice.
Year round all the time.
That's powerful
powerful anti cancer
and.
Like now.
Going
now
present
to present time
what do you normally eat now.
So i tried to stay on
a one meal a day.
Intermittent fasting protocol
but not always
if i work out a lot or just if i'm
hungry I'll have two meals a day.
In it.
In a six hour window
so i still spend a lot of
the day and night of course
fasting.
And as far as food.
Now.
I can have pretty much
any kind of proteins.
And
eggs
no problem.
Chicken.
Fish.
Beef of course.
So and any kind of
animal protein is fine.
I'm still having a hard time with
whole veggies because the fibers.
Still.
Irritates
my my investments
so i still juice my that
is.
The main difference.
Is the sugar.
So.
I eat.
A little bit of sugar
in the form of fruits
and once in a while
in the form of raw honey.
And.
It is something that i didn't
allow myself at all when i was sick.
I am not convinced one
hundred per cent that.
The fructose the
sugar of the fruits.
In it's original foot
mattress which is the whole
truth.
Is really bad for cancer i dunno
but because i didn't know.
I preferred not had
any sugar at all when i was sick
but not in a not sick anymore and i have
zero trace of cancer than older cancer and
inflammatory markers are good.
I have fruits.
On my non workout days
so on my workout days i do more.
Of the
proteins and fats
and on my non
workout days
i do less fat and
a little bit the fruits.
Of course
organic and seasonal
so that's the main difference
with what i didn't before
so my diet is
basically the same.
As far as micronutrients.
A little bit more
variety with the proteins
and a little bit of fruits.
Three times a week.
Got it.
Do you.
Do
you currently take any
probiotics were from
fermented type foods.
Yes i use a Sauerkraut
a lot.
A lot.
A little bit of Sauerkraut.
Almost every day.
So that's so key for your your
gut in the mic since you had.
It was in your digestive system so might
as well support that and that you couldn't
get a better food
than Sauerkraut.
Yeah Sauerkraut is
really one of the thing
that's not on the i
like so it's not it's not.
An effort for me to eat it
and and it's soup for
super powerful as far as as
a pro and prebiotics
so i'm amusing it's.
Quite
often.
Fantastic.
Now i want to bring up another
really really important point and
so if anyone checked
out check back in right
now because this
part is really important.
Before you got cancer
and your diet wasn't that bad
in fact you're.
Doing it
fasting you you're doing.
Keto
the healthy version
for a period of time.
Wish.
It was.
I asked you a question.
What was your stress level and
your stress was off the roof and
and so.
When you do with.
Cancer and.
There are things in a smoking can
cause cancer chemicals cause cancer.
Chronic.
Anything can cause.
Cancer
and bad foods
and things like that.
But.
People don't really.
Put all attention on
the stress factor too so
a stress factor can activate.
Your genetics to.
Turn things in.
A bad way you
can turn things on that
should be turned off so you
went through stress that i think.
Because of the whole
pandemic thing you
couldn't.
You couldn't have your
you had
different doge jazz around the
country that closed down right.
Yes.
Yes absolutely and and
went.
There's a lot of different stresses and
and that's what people don't understand.
I didn't have
what most people would
call a very stressful life
i mean i didn't battle
with
my family i didn't
battle at work i didn't
i didn't have
that kind of stress
and.
Your rights when you said
at my life i was pretty good.
I tried to eat
organic for the past.
I dunno twenty
twenty five years.
I was on keto for
quite a long time.
What else always active
and doing a lot of
meditation are a lot of tai chi.
My martial arts boxing parkour
crossfit
so as i was an active person.
And
doing intermittent
fasting for twenty years.
And.
So people asked me so how come
you did all that and got cancer
and you did all
that and get cured.
And.
I think
i'm not sure but i think it's
the compounding of everything
it's putting everything together
all the time.
And as face trust.
Yes
the
dependent make.
And and the the world
situation stops me from doing
a big part of my
professional activity.
I usually travel the world to to go and
teach in all my nitro Joe's around the world
night
my martial arts goals
i couldn't do that.
It's complicated as far as.
Finance.
And of course that
was a big stressor.
And thats when
the cancer appeared
i also had
a genetic predisposition because
apparently from what the doctor told me.
It was one of the few real
genetic.
Cancer
so my food and my
lifestyle was not so much.
The the the guilty parties there
but to my genetic background was
the sleeping cause as i call it
but distress
was the trigger
that there's no doubt yeah.
And i try my best when i
was trying to heal myself
to compound everything that i knew about
fasting and diet and stuff like that plus
all my new research.
Was with.
Even less stress in my life
you know more breathing more.
Walking out in nature more.
Meditation and stuff
like that then i think it's a
it's a combination
of all the things.
We said last time
on the last video that.
Cancer is multifactorial
but healing cancer
is also multifactorial
and i did a lot of things.
If you add to everything
that we talked about
the ice cold bath.
The breathing
and the walk in nature.
Playing with my dog playing
with my wife having fun laughing.
Watching it nothing
but comedies.
All those things.
I believe participated
to my healing.
You know.
He brought up a good point like you
had to you have to step up your discipline
to to.
To get an ice cold ass i mean for example
fasting for twenty one days that's all
requires a lot of discipline
and you know.
I think come out of necessity.
You understanding.
What needs to be done because
now you did the research.
Out of necessity you pulled it out of yourself
and you're able to kind of stick to it
because you're probably
willing to do whatever it took.
To survive basically
yes
yes absolutely
and the.
Some people say abbott is probably because
of your martial arts training you have
more discipline than others.
It might be true
but look at gaia
our friend guy
who is.
Who was seventy
at the time of his cancer
and
no discipline whatsoever
never breakfast any martial arts.
Overweight
cancer stage four
and diabetes
everything you
could have he had it
and he did the same thing
as me he did the fat
thing he did the keto
and and
he cured himself
so.
Like you said out of necessity
when your life is on the line
i think it's much much easier
than when
you just.
Randomly decide to do a
fast or randomly decide to
to
as as as a prevention to
take care of your health.
And don't get me wrong
prevention is critical
and it's much better much
easier than finding a cancer
but.
But
it's harder
it's hot too fast.
When.
When you don't have.
A.
Very very high motivation
such as eight you're gonna die.
You know
people that are watching
this video right now are.
Either potentially have cancer.
They're interested in
preventing cancer that
might have friends or
family that have cancer
but if cancer is
not on your radar.
Because you're not.
You don't have
any awareness of it
it'll never happen to me even
though it's the number one second.
Or the second.
Killer
world.
And.
You probably won't be
interested in cancer until you.
Have you to someone
close to you or yourself
can you start developing
cancer and then.
You become very
interested in it.
So.
It wasn't i wasn't into health
at all until i had probably my
late twenties.
Because i personally was
affected negatively with my health
other people
they seemed to
get by and they can.
They don't have any problems until
later in life and then they they make this
shift and change.
So.
My whole thing is awesome.
You can.
Acquire
a tremendous amount of
survival knowledge by
learning from other people's.
Stories.
Others people's success
successful actions other
people's strategies and.
I dunno if.
When you're watching
this you realize how.
Vital
and Fred is
giving us this
this really key is these keys
are these strategies because.
It can come in handy if
you have your kid cancer.
Wherever you have someone
going through cancer this is like.
Superior information
that you should.
Use
and apply and think with
and.
Cause there's nothing worse than getting
cancer and not having any of this data could
you imagine like.
Getting cancer
not having all these insights
and you just falling mainstream.
Which
you're you know you pray i
dunno if you'd be alive by now.
Yet
absolutely
and you know
we're so lucky to live.
In the times we're living
because imagine my situation
without the Internet
a right.
Right
what would i have
done i mean nothing.
Right.
That's right so.
So again it comes down to.
Being able to.
Somehow with your awareness.
Pull out the right
information that makes
sense to you because there's
so much confusion out there
and unfortunately
and.
The first
five to ten pages of Google has.
What the what
everyone's doing and i
i think with the thing that
helped me mostly as a
i'm always skeptical of what everyone
else is doing or everyone thinks is true.
It's usually the opposite.
Especially when you get into the
single everyone knows yeah well
who's everyone and
where did that come from so.
I suspect that i.
I tend to do.
Everything the opposite and
it seems to be very successful.
Very successful.
I remember
i think it was one of your
videos when you said you have.
I don't remember what he was i think it was
about diabetes if you have diabetes go on
the website of the American diabetes
association and do the complete opposite then
you have a better chance.
I apologize if it's someone
else i don't remember
but i thought that was brilliant
and that's basically what i did
he doesn't mean that
i completely rejected.
Western medicine
or that i have a grudge
against against it.
I just didn't think it
was the answer for me
but
as we discussed last time
i
i did.
Three sessions of chemo.
Because of the pain and it
really helped me so i'm thankful
to to those doctors
and
nurse.
Who who are helping with the
symptoms and it is critical when you.
When you soft when
you suffer so much that.
You don't
you're not even sure
that you want to leave.
And thats where i
was at some point.
And a doctor tells you hair.
Take my chemo take my feeling you're
going to feel better in in three weeks.
It's a miracle
and i and i really appreciated
and i thank my doctor for that
but.
As far as curing me
without any long
term side effects.
For me.
Western medicine was not the answer
and i choose to look at the biology
and the and the and the science
instead of the medicine
but he doesn't mean it's the same truth for
anyone everybody has to make his research
and and put.
His or her trust.
Into what feels right
for for for that person.
When you deal with cancer
there's a lot of conflicting
information so you have.
A lot of
so called facts that are
opposing each
other you can't have.
Two facts opposing each
other one of them has to be.
False
and so you you unfortunately
going to have to study both
viewpoints.
Back and forth to really see which
one is true and which ones are false but
when you deal with cancer
there's a lot of money going on
and there's a lot of corruption.
There's a lot of them.
False information
manipulation of research.
So.
There's a.
There's a really good book
i'm gonna put a down below
of them.
Some one really
highly credible scientists who.
Talked about all the manipulation that
they do in cancer research and i think.
If you're
really.
Interested you should take
a look at that book because
you need to know
the truth
and.
And that way you can em.
You know not be susceptible
to doing the wrong thing.
One of the thing that i did when i
was doing my research and it's.
Just it was my main philosophy.
It's not always true but i was my
main line to select information is
when you have two conflicting
informations about
the exact same thing.
First.
Trust the one that
doesn't make money.
Like you're fasting.
Trusting doesn't make
anyone any money
so studied at first it
doesn't mean it's the truth.
Keep studying.
All possibilities
but my first attention
would be on those.
Research and from researchers
that didn't make money out of it.
That was my first to
my first main idea.
Yet unfortunately others
researches.
They get paid they're
they're funded by
industry and.
Governments and
things like that so
i mean who's going to
pay a researcher to do.
Research on somebody
doesn't make money it's it's
it's hard to.
There's so many things like
that is why you're not going
to find a lot of research in.
Apple cider vinegar for example
because some it's just not.
Not a product that people buy.
So anyway Fred this
has been an incredible.
Knowledge.
Talk.
Dialogue that we had i think
people are going to really.
Use this data to
survive better and.
I'll put some down some
links if he hadn't saw.
If he had
not seen the other videos that we've done
are related to this topic so you can have
all information so.
Thank you very much read.
I appreciate you my pleasure
thank you.